Guide to the Palladium Flyers Collection MSS 441
Fales Library and Special Collections
Palladium Flyers Collection
ca. 1985 -1987
MSS 441
Fales Library and Special Collections
2.5 linear feet (2 boxes)
From its opening in 1985 through the late 1980s, New York City's Palladium was one of the major features in the New York club scene, providing a venue for many different events. The Palladium Flyers Collection consists of flyers and posters for photographic, art, and fashion exhibitions and receptions as well as book publication releases, live performances, and parties. The scope of this collection gives insight to the distinct position of The Palladium nightclub and its involvement in the Downtown New York scene.
Palladium (Nightclub).
Historical Note
The Palladium, formerly known as the Academy of Music, was a concert hall that transitioned into a night club in New York City. Located at East 14th Street, it served as a "hot spot" that catered to the downtown "new wave music" movement. From its opening in May 1985 through the end of the 1980s, Palladium was reserved as one of the major features in the New York club scene, providing a venue for varied events, ranging from live performances and parties to cultural exhibitions and publication celebrations.
After closing in 1997, New York University converted this landmark into a residence hall and athletic facility for undergraduate students.
Scope and Content
The Palladium Flyer Collection consists of flyers and posters for photographic, artistic, and fashion exhibitions and receptions as well as book publication releases, live performances, and parties. The collection documents the diverse nature of The Palladium nightclub and its service to the Downtown New York community.
This collection features celebrations hosted and attended by Stephen Saban, Michael Musto, Jeffrey Sanker, John Sex, Anita Sarko, and others.
The collection is divided into 7 series and corresponding oversize materials:
Series I: Photographic Exhibitions and Receptions contains flyers and/or posters to photographic exhibitions and various receptions hosted by different contributors.
Series II: Publication Releases and Receptions contains flyers and/or posters to book and magazine releases and receptions.
Series III: Art Exhibitions and Receptions contains flyers and/or posters to the art installations, exhibitions, and receptions that were both privately and publicly featured in Palladium.
Series IV: Fashion Exhibitions contains flyers and/or posters to fashsion shows and presentations to various fashion collections.
Series V: Theatrical and Dance Performances contains flyers and/or posters to ballet performances and play productions presented at the Palladium venue.
Series VI: Musical Performances contains flyers and/or posters to concerts to domestic and international acts and their after parties.
Series VII: Parties contains flyers and/or posters to birthday celebrations, anniversaries, and themed events.
Arrangement
The Palladium flyers are arranged primarily at the folder level, divided into series based on the event. Folder titles are based on hosts and event title. At times titles were altered for the sake of uniformity. Oversize materials were removed from their original locations to allow for adequate housing and can be found in the oversize series in the finding aid. There is only one object, a plastic knife that was sent out as an invitation, which is housed in series VII.
Series I: Photographic Exhibitions and Receptions
Series II: Publication Releases and Receptions
Series III: Art Exhibitions and Receptions
Series IV: Fashion Exhibitions
Series V: Theatrical and Dance Performances
Series VI: Musical Performances
Series VII: Parties
OVERSIZE Series I: Photographic Exhibitions and Receptions
OVERSIZE Series II: Publication Releases and Receptions
OVERSIZE Series III: Art Exhibitions and Receptions
OVERSIZE Series IV: Fashion Exhibitions
OVERSIZE Series V: Theatrical and Dance Performances
OVERSIZE Series VI: Musical Performances
OVERSIZE Series VII: Parties
The arrangement was assembled chronologically by date. Materials without a year are arranged at the end of each series, in order by month.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Related Archival Materials note
Downtown Flyers and Invitations
April Palmieri Papers
Franklin Furnace Ephemera Collection
Nelson Sullivan Video Collection
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The collection was purchased by NYU's Fales Library & Special Collections from a bookseller in 2015.
Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Baldessari, John Anthony; Brooklyn Academy of Music.; Brooklyn Museum.; Guerrilla Girls (Group of artists).; Haring, Keith; King, Stephen, 1947-; Leo Castelli Gallery.; Mabou Mines (Theater group).; Musto, Michael, 1955-; Palladium (Nightclub).; Sex, John; Straub, Peter, 1943-; Sur Rodney, (Sur); Tony Shafrazi Gallery.; Tseng, Kwong Chi; Wong, Martin; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities) |z New York (State) |z New York.; Art |x Exhibitions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Broadsides (notices); Music |z New York (State) |z New York.; Performance art |z New York (State) |z New York.; Photography |x Exhibitions |z New York (State) |z New York.
- Series I: Photographic Exhibitions and Receptions
  - Taking Pictures Is Fun: An Exhibition By David La Chapelle, September 11, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Steven Style and Stacie Teele: An Exhibition of Photographs By Sylvia Plachy, February 5, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stacie Teele and Steven Style: An Exhibition of Photography By Patrick McMullan, March 19, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Patrick McMullan Photography Exhibition, March 19- April 26, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - POSSESSIONS By Christopher Makos, March 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LAST DANCE: Glamour, Death, and Entertainment, April 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Opening of Weirld Beauty: The Photo Exhibition, September 27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Art and Politics: The Photo Exhibition by Gianfranco Gorgoni, October 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Brooklyn Museum: Celebration of Exhibition "The Machine Age In America, 1918- 1941", October 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Fine Art of Paparazzi and Portraiture: A Photgraphic Exhibition of Celebrity Faces and Figures By America's Foremost Photographers, July 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series II: Publication Releases and Receptions
  - Nasty Habits on Time Square: A Publication Party for Josh Alan Friedman's New Book "Tales of Time Square", July 10, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Doubleday & Company: Celebrate the Publication of "Street Art" By Allan Schwartzman, October 12, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - East Village Eye: New Words, December 21, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Random House: Celebrate the Publication of "Good Morning Blue: The Autobiography of Count Basie" with Performances By The Count Basie Orchestra and Joe Williams, January 17, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Celebrate the Publication of Andy Warhol's 1986 Edition of "Cowboys and Indians", April 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Egret and Roland Hagenberg: First Edition of "Soho. A Guide. A Documentary", April 26, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Random House: A Publication Party for Michael Musto's "DOWNTOWN", May 28, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Social Disease: Paul Rudnick's First Novel Published By Alfred A. Knop, June 6, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Eric Fischl and Jerry Saltz: The Publication of their "Sketchbook With Voices", June 24, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Joey Arias, Patti Astor, Fred Brathwaite, Edit deAk: Publication of "Art After Midnight: The East Village Scene", June 25, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Editors of ID Magazine: Gala Celebration of the Best Designs of the Year and the Publication of the 1986 ID Magazine Design Review, August 14, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stephan Saban and Michael Musto: Celebrate the Publication of Cynthia Heimel's New Book "But Enough About You: Avoiding Fabulousness", October 23, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Joseph Papp, Stephan DiLaura, M. Stephan Doherty Celebrate American Artist Magazine's 50th Year of Publication: Party Honoring Paul Davis, Art Director of the New York Shakespeare Festival, January 21, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Jay McInerney and Gary Fisketjon: Celebrate the Publication of "The Sportswriter" By Richard Ford, March 21 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mary Peacock & Yolanda Cuomo: See the First of Vue: The Village Voice Fashion Magazine, April 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Palladium: Gold and Silver Cotillion Dance to Celebrate the Publication of "The Debutante's Guide to Life", June 19 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Celebrate the Publication of John Water's New Book "Crackpot", October 22 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Crown Publishers Inc. and Nikki Haskell: Sharon Churcher's "New York Confidential- The Lowdown on the Big Town", November 20 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Series III: Art Exhibitions and Receptions
  - The Whitney Museum of American Art: Reception for the Exhibition "High Styles: 20th Century American Design", September 19, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Celebrate With Designers Downtown In Honor of Future, Lighting, Textiles, October 9, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Guerrilla Girls: The Women Artists Terrorist Organization, October 17, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tony Shafrazi and Leo Castelli: Dinner Honoring Keith Haring, October 26, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alan Belcher/ Cable, November 14, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Kitchen: Opening of New Art and Performance Space Following the Premiere of New Ice Nights, January 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Post- Opening Reception for Artists Participating in the B-side Gallery Exhibition: POP- KORN, January 24,1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Brooklyn Museum Private Reception for the Artists Following the Member's Preview of the Exhibition "The Public and Private: American Prints Today", February 6, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 49th Parallel Centre for Contemporary Canadian Art: Celebrate 5th Anniversary of Gallery and Opening of "Icarus: The Vision of Angels", an exhibition in collaboration with Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, March 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Post- Opening of CRASH: Exhibition of New Paintings At the Sydney Janis Gallery, March 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Meet Architect Professor Ettore Sottsass: The Milan Style for Ceramique Francois, November 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Paul & Melissa Eidia and the Artist of the Starving Artists' Cookbook Video Screening and Exhibition, April 3, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Steven Styles and Stacie Teele: The Staircase Mural Series, April 18, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Palladium: Post- Opening Party for the Hugh Piney Gallery Exhibition, February 8 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Vito Acconci & Palladium Underground: Garden of Plants and Bodies Opening Party Honoring the Artist, June 25 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Double Group Exhibition/Fine and Functional Art: "Illuminations: The Art of Our Future", September 17 & 18 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Blue China: An Art and Fashio Performance, September 18 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery: A Post- Opening Celebration in Honor of George Segal, September 27 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Series IV: Fashion Exhibitions
  - Diane Brill Menswear Presents Her "New Millionaire$ Club" Spring- Summer '86, August 21, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - London Designers Collective, August 22, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Katharine Hammett: Think Global Autumn/Winter '85 Collection, September 12, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - East Village Eye, Vito Bruno, Winterwear, and Webo: A Party Introducing New Fashions and a New Way to Dance, October 23, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Andre Walker: Fall Study '86, May 8, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - The New Look: Party Celebrating New York Fashion Week, November 5, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Julia Morton and Paul Monroe Present: "Hollywood Heroes and Heroines" and An Evening of Einstein's Fashion, January 7, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Jeffrey Sanker Presents "The Rich Bitch Collection '87" By Frank Composto, January 11, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Palladium Presents Diane Pernet: Spring- Summer '87 Fashion Show, January 15, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Palladium Presents Diane Pernet: Spring- Summer '87 Fashion Show, January 15, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Jeffrey Sanker: Jhane Barnes' Men's and Women's Fall '87 Collection, April 5, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Series V: Theatrical and Dance Performances
  - Gaultier Chopinot Presents the American Premiere of Le Defile Ballet, June 18- 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - A Reception Celebrating the American Premiere of Le Defile, June 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The American Friends of Covent Garden, The Royal Ballet, The Brooklyn Academy of Music, and The Sadler's Wells Association Post Performance Party Honoring Sadler's Wells Royal Ballet, February 5, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dead Women: The Terminal Musical, August 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - All Saints Day of Haoui Montaug's "No Entiendes", November 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Gabriel Rotello Presents Scott Wittman's "Rauncho Notorious", December 11, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Haoui Montaug's: "No Entiendes", December 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Palladium and Goethe House of New York: "Tingel, Tangel, Kabaretts: 750 Years of Berlin", January 18, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Haoui Montaug's "No Entiendes" with Co- Host Anita Sarko, February 21 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - American Friends of the Paris Opera & Ballet and Palladium: Reception Honoring Rudolf Nureyev and the Paris Opera Ballet, July 9 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - "Pagan Place": A Scott Witman Production, August 7 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Paula Cooper: A Celebration In Honor of Robert Wilson on the Occasion of the Brooklyn Academy of Music's New Wave Festival Production of "The Golden Windows", October 24 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Series VI: Musical Performances
  - Ric Ocasek, Veronique Cartier, Marie- Helene du Chastel, Larry Uttal: Premiere Performance of Antonia de Portago's New Band "Antonia", February 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Palladium Presents A Concert At Midnight: Bo Diddley, March 6, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Palladium Invites You to the American Premiere of "Mystery Girls", June 26, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Public Image LTD Concert, July 23, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Adrian Belew: Live in Concert, September 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Carlos Alomar of the David Bowie Band: An Evening of Sight and Sound, September 10, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - The American Premiere of Sigue Sigue Sputnik: Halloween, October 22, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Drag Aid: The Celebrity Concert Fundraising Benefit for Aids Research and Support, October 30, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Palladium Presents The American Premiere of Sigue Sigue Sputnik, October 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Live in Concert! Palladium Presents the American Premiere of Sigue Sigue Sputnick: A Halloween of Fifth Generation Rock & Roll, October 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Post- Concert Party for Fela Anikulapo Kuti, November 8, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Palladium Presents "The Bongos: Live in Concert", January 14, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - "Let the Music Take Control", March 18, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Eye and Ear Theater Present Two Evenings of Performance, Music and Dance to Benefit the 1988 Production of Allen Ginsberg's "Kaddish", May 18 and 20, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Palladium Presents Baba Olatunji and His 16 Piece Dance Percussion Ensemble, March 11 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Techno- Primitive: First New York Appearance of Chris & Cosey, April 25 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - The New York Philharmonic, Palladium, an Frank Zappa Present Horizons '86: Music as Theater, May 19 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - The Mamas and the Papas in Concert and Publication of John Phillips Autobiography "Papa John", June 7 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Palladium Open: Miniature Golf Featuring the 19th Hole Orchestra, August 14 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Live in Concert: Trouble Funk, September 17 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Series VII: Parties
  Scope and Content
  Parties contains flyers and/or posters to birthday celebrations, anniversaries, and themed events.
  - The Director and Staff of the New Music Seminar: Party Marking the Opening of "The Sixth New Music Seminar", September 25, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Celebration of Paul Morrissey's New Film "Mixed Blood", October 18, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Happy Valley Rest Home, October 31, 1985 (Box 1, Object ID: 441.2.0001)
  - Stephen Saban, Beauregard Houston- Montgomery, Alan Rish, and Rudolf: Michael Musto's Birthday Party, December 18, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Honoring Grace Jones: The Release of Her New Manhattan/Island Album and Video "Slave To The Rhythm", December 20, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Michael Limbo: Sur Rodney Sur's Birthday Party & "Hallmark Through the Eyes of the East Village"- A Birthday Card Art Installation, December 27, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Brooke Alexander: Post- Opening Celebration for Richard Mock, January 4, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Palladium: Celebrate the 15th Year of Electronic Arts Intermix as a Center for Artist' Video, January 23, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Antia Sarko and Tseng Kwong Chi: Pre-carnival Soca Jump Up, January 24, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Anita Sarko: A Dime- A- Dance, February 6, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Palladium: A Valentine Birthday Party for Holly Solomon, February 12, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Female Beauty Round the World: Greatest Collection of Strange & Secret Photograph Rudolf's Top 40 Birthday Burlesque!, February 26, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Anita Sarko Presents "Viva Las Vegas", March 28, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Anita Sarko: NY TALK's 2nd Anniversary Party, April 2, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Dianne Brill's Birthday Bash and Cocktail Reception at the Men's Club, April 16 and 18, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Anita Sarko, Stephen Saban, Rudolf Invite you to "Beliner Cabaret Night", May 9, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - A Party Celebrating the Fashion Video Awards, May 15, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Beach Blanket Blow- Out, May 24, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Anita Sarko Presents The Friday the 13th Voodoo Jungle Party, June 13, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - An Invitation to Give You DELIRIUM! Hosted by St. Martin's London, June 21, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Gabriel Rotello & Justin Ross Present Hot Grease, August 7, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Party Honoring Judas Priest Celebrating Fuel For Life Tour, August 30, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Mimi and Jerry Rubin: The New Friday Fall Party, September 12 & 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - 1986 NEXT WAVE Festival Opening Night: Celebrating the 125 Anniversary Season of the Brooklyn Academy of Music, October 7, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Atlantic City Night Celebrating the World Premiere of "The Color of Money", October 8, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Champagne Reception to Celebrate the Creation of the Taittinger: 1983 Vintage Botte, November 15, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Happy Thanksgiving, November 26, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Perri Lister, Andriana Kaegi, Cheryl Poitier: Party Honoring the Winner of Playgirl's 1987 Search for the Sexiest Man in New York, December 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Jeffrey Sanker Presents "Hungover and Broke", January 1, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Michael Alig Presents the 2nd Annual Filthy Mouth Contest, January 18, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - "Circle The Wagons! Protect the Women and Children and Come on Down to the Ho- Down", February 6, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Randy Jones of the Village People and Maria Benevenuti: Wrestling Press International's Man of the Year! American Hero!, February 25, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Anita Sarko: The First Annual Gilles De Rais and Sinners Costume Ball, March 14, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Anita Sarko and Tseng Kwong Chi: Return to the Jungle, April 4, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Reception Celebrating Carmen D'Alessio's Birthday, October 18, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Performance of La Mama's Original Cotton Club- Gala, January 31 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Semaphore: Celebration Honoring Futura 2000 and Martin Wong, February 5 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Rudolf's Top 40, February 26 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Victory Production Presents: The Premiere Transexual Beauty Pageant, March 12 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - The Prince and Princess Egon von Furstenberg Celebrate Third Wedding Anniversary, March 19 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Ileana Sonnabend; Party for John Baldessari, April 5 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Sandro Chia's Birthday, April 19 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Komar and Melamid Present May Day Celebration, May 1 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Thierry Mugler Presents "The First Anniversary of Palladium", May 14 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Jack Gallery: Post- Opening Celebration Honoring Peter Max, May 28 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Charles Cowles, Christopher Ford, Manuel E. Gonzalez, Holly and Horace Solomon Invite You to the Michael Todd Room, June 6 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Pinup Girl: Dianne Brill's Birthday Party, June 11 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Paper: Second Anniversary Issue! Youth Power Rules, June 11 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Opening Party of the Seventh New Music Seminar, July 13 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Anita Sarko: A Night of Tropical Enchantment, July 30 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Party for New Order, August 1 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Lisa E., Michael Musto, Anita Sarko, Alan Rish, and Andy Anderson: Thank Heaven for Little Girls! A Birthday Party for James St. James, August 6 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Palladium Presents an Evening With Pete Shelley, August 27 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Evening with Eddie Murphy, August 27 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Cinevista: Party in Hono of Derek Jarman, Sarah Radclyffe, Tilde Swinton, and Spencer Leigh Celebrating the Premiere of "Caravaggio", August 28 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Anita Sarko: 2nd Annual Pajama Party, September 13 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Palladium Celebrates the Birthday of Leo Castelli, September 19 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - John Sex's New Twelve- inch "Bump and Grind" On Varla Records, September 25 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Ikon Films: Celebrates the Mabou Mines "Dead End Kids" and the 8th Annual American Independent Film Market, October 3 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Party for Judy Rifka, October 12 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Stephen King and Peter Straub on the Eve of Halloween, October 30 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - 8BC, November 15 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Palladium Cordially Invites You to Unfold the New Year, December 31 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Palladium Card: Pink "L", Undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Mailing List Notification, Undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Photographic Exhibitions and Receptions
  - "Last Dance", April 10- May 4, 1985 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - "Weird Beauty", September 1985 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - "Art and Politics: The Photo Exhibition" By Gianfranco Gorgoni, October 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Publication Releases and Receptions
  - Grove Press, Bomb Magazine, and Brooklyn Academy of Music: Celebration Honoring Kathy Acker's "The Birth of a Poet", December 6, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Celebrate Fall Issue Bomb Magazine, October 19 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Art Exhibitions and Receptions
  - Palladium Exhibition- Curated By: Guerrila Girls: The Women Artist Terrorist Organization, October 17, 1985 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - "Pictures From The Inner Mind": Art Exhibition Designed In The Tradition of the Surrealist's Salon of the 1930s, January 3, 1986 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - Nepboman 1986- Palladium (Box 2, Folder 4)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Theatrical and Dance Performances
  - 1985 Next Wave Festival (Box 2, Folder 5)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Musical Performances
  - Palladium Midnight Concerts: Tuxedo Moon, May 22, 1986 (Map-case 2D, Folder 1)
  - Palladium Midnight Concerts- Einsurzende Nubauten, May 26, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)